https://www.discount-essiac-tea.com/privacy-policy.html

Home
Ordering InfoORDER ESSIACOrdering GuideBuying on AmazonLow Price GuaranteeMoney Back GuaranteeIngredientsNutrition FactsCapsulesSteviaPricesRequest BrochureWholesaleAffiliate ProgramNew! *CBD*Special Offers*Deal* Essiac + CBD
Product InfoOrder Essiac TodayProof We're AuthenticWhy Powdered Herbs?Ty Bollinger's DocumentaryEssiac 101Sheep Sorrel RootImmune SystemGenuine Essiac ChecklistWhy Us: 6 reasonsMyths...Busted!The Essiac ReportHerb QualityRed CloverBenefits of EssiacBrewing InstructionsSuppliesEssiac Tea DosageEssiac For PetsEight Herb EssiacEssiac Taking TipsAuthentic EssiacEssiac Tea FAQDetoxFor ChildrenHelpful HintsRene Caisse DocumentaryEssiac Pronounciation and DefinitionPressBlogTestimonialsAbout UsContact Us
search tips
advanced search
search engine by
freefind
Privacy Policy
Last updated 7/10/2020 by: Gina PaulhusWe take our privacy policy very seriously.Discount-essiac-tea.com has always been committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your personal and corporate information. We have established Privacy Principles to govern our use of customer information. Discount-essiac-tea.com does not sell, share or distribute Customer Information to any third party organization. Accountability Discount-essiac-tea.com is responsible for maintaining and protecting customer information under its control. Identifying PurposesThe purposes for which customer information is collected shall be identified before or at the time the information is collected. ConsentThe knowledge and consent of the customer are required for the collection, use or disclosure of customer information except where required or permitted by law. Limiting Collection The customer information collected must be limited to those details necessary for the purposes identified by (Company Name) Information must be collected by fair and lawful means. Limiting Use, Disclosure and RetentionCustomer information may only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was collected unless the customer has otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law. Customer information may only be retained for the period of time required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. AccuracyCustomer information must be maintained in as accurate, complete and up-to-date form as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is to be used. Safeguarding Customer Information Customer information must be protected by security safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity level of the information. OpennessDiscount-essiac-tea.com is required to make information available to customers concerning the policies and practices that apply to the management of their information. Customer Access Upon request, a customer shall be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of their information, and shall be given access to it. Customers may verify the accuracy and completeness of their information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate. Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions Customers may direct any questions or inquiries with respect to the privacy principles outlined above or about our practices by contacting the designated person(s) accountable for privacy at Discount-essiac-tea.com.
Privacy Policy:  Unsubscribe/Opt-Out
Unsubscribe/OPT Out
If you would like to unsubscribe, please contact us.
Bryan and Gina Paulhus, owners
New! Comments
Have your say about what you just read! Leave me a comment in the box below.
×
Thanks for stopping by! to keep up with the latest in essiac news as well as receive coupon codes, sign up here!
Email
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe
Don't worry - we never share information with third parties, and we only send out about 6 issues per year.
HomeOrdering InfoORDER ESSIACOrdering GuideBuying on AmazonLow Price GuaranteeMoney Back GuaranteeIngredientsNutrition FactsCapsulesSteviaPricesRequest BrochureWholesaleAffiliate ProgramNew! *CBD*Special Offers*Deal* Essiac + CBDProduct InfoOrder Essiac TodayProof We're AuthenticWhy Powdered Herbs?Ty Bollinger's DocumentaryEssiac 101Sheep Sorrel RootImmune SystemGenuine Essiac ChecklistWhy Us: 6 reasonsMyths...Busted!The Essiac ReportHerb QualityRed CloverBenefits of EssiacBrewing InstructionsSuppliesEssiac Tea DosageEssiac For PetsEight Herb EssiacEssiac Taking TipsAuthentic EssiacEssiac Tea FAQDetoxFor ChildrenHelpful HintsRene Caisse DocumentaryEssiac Pronounciation and DefinitionPressBlogTestimonialsAbout UsContact Us
Email
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe
High Quality Organic Essiac Tea...at Discount Prices.*New* Instant Savings when you bundle Essiac and CBD.TestimonialsThe Importance of Sheep Sorrel RootEssiac on YouTube
Recent Articles
International Shipping Costs of Essiac Nov 12, 20 12:37 PMThe international shipping costs of essiac are certainly something to consider
Read More
Why Essiac is Not Cheaper on Amazon Nov 10, 20 06:26 PMLearn why essiac is not cheaper on amazon. See our cost comparison for authentic essiac on amazon versus essiac on discount-essiac-tea.com. Read More
Percentage of Sheep Sorrel Root in Essiac Nov 04, 20 05:08 PMLearn what the ideal percentage of Sheep Sorrel Root is in Essiac Read More
Click here to contact us, or call Toll-Free: 1-866-ESSIAC1 (377-4221).
Copyright 2020 by Gina Paulhus. All rights reserved. Phone: 1-978-504-9517 or toll free: 1-866-ESSIAC1 (377-4221)
